ODEDEYI, Olukemi Theresa

+234-8169282416|Olu.Odedeyi@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/odedevi-olukemi-0b16a47b/ Adedoyin Street, Off Shipeolu street, Palmgrove, Lagos State

CAREER SUMMARY:

Human resource enthusiast, dedicated and resilient individual with experience and strong professional background in import logistics, customer service/client relationship and satisfaction, product quality assurance and also knowledgeable in Structured Ouery Language (SOL) and digital communication skills.

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Proficient in IT Support responsibilities such as using basic SQL functions, command lines and scripting to proffer solutions to human resource related tasks.
- Providing technical support for the overall human resource team and customer relations including responding to calls, emails and resolving issues from customers.
- Providing technical and IT support to the overall operations and logistics team and clientele management.
- **TOOLS:** Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint and Outlook)

WORK EXPERIENCE/ CAREER HISTORY

Front End Development Intern at Zuri Training Program.

(Mar 2021 - Till date)

Roles and Responsibilities

- Attended online classes for fundamentals of front-end development given by mentors.
- Completed task on Responsive web design, pushed to GitHub and GitHub pages.
- Used code pen to fork and create a CSS style sheet for a form task as given by a mentor.
- Attempted a google homepage replication task and a portfolio creation task.
- Carried out further tasks and projects as assigned by mentors.

Customer Relationship Officer at Smashrides Solution Services, Ikeja.

(Oct 2019 - Dec 2019)

Roles and Responsibilities

- Coordinated customer service activities within the company by making calls, ensuring and maintaining healthy client relationships.
- Managed the customer service department of the company under the supervision and guidance of my line manager.
- Sourced for clients and investors for the company and maintained logs and spreadsheets for all activities
- Carried out other assignments given to me and reported directly to my line manager

Logistics Personnel at *V - Logic Forwarding & Clearing Limited, Ikeja* Roles and Responsibilities (Jan 2018 - Sept 2019)

Managed all new and existing client documentation and served as a source of information and feedback for the organization, alongside shipping and terminal invoices and facilitating payment.

- Developed standard operating methods to manage transport operations efficiently thereby enabling effective implementation of transportation plans.
- Acted in a supervisory role when necessitated to facilitate job progress and assisted in capturing data needed for duty assessment and monitoring.
- With the supervision of Head of operations and operations manager, facilitated job progress and delivery.
- Ensured that all activities and transactions were carried out seamlessly and yielded positive results and carried out any other activity designated to me.

Front Desk Personnel/Operations Assistant at *V – Logic Forwarding & Clearing Limited, Ikeja* (March 2017 – Dec 2017) *Roles and Responsibilities*

- Attended to and received visitors at the reception area warmly and notified staff members of visitors' arrival and scheduled appointments within the company.
- Conducted bank transactions on behalf of the company when directed.
- Managed and monitored sales trend on the e-commerce platform, attended to and resolved customers inquiries and complaints promptly.
- Supported all procurement transactions and analyzed them for conformity with specified requirements and conducted monthly physical inventory of products in the warehouse.
- Followed-up on purchases orders status and kept my supervisor abreast with estimated time of delivery of goods: ensured that all expected goods were received in accordance with POs specifications and in good condition.
- Carried out any other task assigned.

Quality Control and Assurance Trainee at *Top Crust Bakery Nigeria Limited, Ikeja.*(Mar 2012 - Aug 2012)

(Mar 2013 - Aug 2013) Roles and Responsibilities

- Worked on new recipes and ideas that brought about new inventions in making of some bakery products.
- Conducted experiments to determine compatibility of new materials and produce samples to test and develop to meet company standards and criteria.
- I monitored the entire production process to ensure standards and HACCPs were met and adhered to.
- Worked closely with the bakery manager and chief operating officer to ensure compliance of all staff members in the production unit and carried out other assignments given.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

Bachelor of Science (BSc.) Food Science (2014)

University of Ilorin, Ilorin, Nigeria.

OTHER PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified **Procurement and Logistics certificate** CILT (UK), 2019
- Soft skills training certificate Jobberman Nigeria, 2020

• Human Resource Management Certificate, Ace Coterie Consulting Nigeria, 2020

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Energetic self-starter with strong technical and organizational skills. Ability to initiate as a team builder and team player. Excellent in problems-solving, and operations management.

INTERESTS:

Reading, Music, Research, Travelling.

LANGUAGES SPOKEN:

- > English Fluent
- Yoruba Fluent